sydex.net 2018-12-26

# Sydex.net: Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

## A. INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM YOU

### 1\. Why do we collect information?

We collect information in order to provide useful products and services to you and others. We also use this data to improve the quality of those products and services.

### 2\. What kinds of information do you collect?

We collect information that (i) you provide to us or authorize us to collect as a result of using our products ( _e.g._ social media accounts, call and text logs, etc.) and (ii) information about your use of our products and services (e.g., browser type, search categories, location).

### 3\. How do you use the information you collect?

We use information to (i) provide useful products and services, such as Sydex, caller ID applications, and customer support, to our users; (ii) verify public information and information obtained from other sources; and (iii) help us analyze usage and effectiveness of our products and services.

### 4\. With whom do you share the information you collect and why?

Besides the consumer users of our products and services, we provide access to information to our business users ( _e.g._ , customer support centers, corporate fraud departments) so that they may identify and verify their customers. We provide access to information to third party partners of ours in order to provide our products and services to you. Further, we also provide access to non-personally-identifiable information to our third party advertisers so that they can deliver relevant online and mobile advertising to you (more information about third party advertising is provided below).

### 5\. How do I stop the collection of my information?

In order to stop further collection of information by us, you will need to stop using our products and services.

### 6\. Where do you get your information from?

Publicly Available Information Sources: This is information that's available to the public. It includes addresses, street names, cities, states and ZIP codes. Other examples of publicly available information include published phone directories and information published on the Internet, such as publicly available social network profiles.

Third-Party Data Suppliers: Information from third-party data suppliers originates from a variety of sources. It may include publicly available information, such as phone directories, as well as information from other sources. For example, people often provide name, address, phone number, email address and other personal information when filling out forms for contests, sweepstakes, subscriptions or other similar offers. Often, this information can be shared with third parties. Whenever you provide personal information - either online or offline - you should understand how the information will be used and whether it can be shared with third parties.

## B. INFORMATION COLLECTED BY THIRD PARTIES

### 1\. What information is collected by third parties?

Third parties may collect information during your visits to our websites and use of our mobile products and services. Such information includes searches you perform ( _e.g._ , category of business, location) and general information about you ( _e.g._ , browser type, mobile device type, unique user ID, mobile carrier, IP address, date and time of your visits, locality, pages viewed). Certain products and services may collect specific information such as your name, phone number, IP address, etc., but unless you provide specific details about yourself, information collected by such third parties will generally be limited to non-personally-identifiable information.

### 2\. How is information collected by third parties?

Third parties may collect information by using cookies, web beacons, performance-measuring phone numbers, or GPS information. A cookie is a small file that contains a unique ID tag and stores information ( _e.g._ , pages visited, information voluntarily provided). A web beacon is a small graphic file used to identify if a page has been viewed. A performance measuring phone number involves collection of call-related information such as originating phone number and call duration. GPS informationmay include city, state and other information when you use our products or services on a GPS-enabled mobile device.

### 3\. Why do these third parties collect information?

Third parties may collect information in order to (i) deliver relevant online and mobile advertising to you both on and off our sites; (ii) help us provide or analyze usage and effectiveness of our products and services; and (iii) for their own business purposes ( _e.g._ , such as to report aggregate, non-personally identifiable information about the use of their services and technologies).

### 4\. How will they use the information they collect? Will they share it?

Collection and use of data is subject to the privacy policies of those third party companies, such as the privacy policy of [AdMarvel](http://www.admarvel.com/AdMarvel_Privacy_Policy_2012.pdf) or [Google](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/). Accordingly, please review those policies for specific information.

### 5\. How do I stop the collection and use of my information by third parties?

To stop collection of information in connection with the use of our products and services, you will need to stop using them. To opt-out of Sydex mobile app marketing program tracking, [click here](https://www.optoutmobile.com/optOut). To stop collection of browsing information via supporting web browsers, [click here](http://donottrack.us/). To stop information collection for purposes of relevant online advertising, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). At this time, there is no industry solution to opt-out of receiving relevant mobile advertising.

To opt out of tracking on Sydex mobile app marketing programs, go to our third party provideris website by [clicking here](https://www.optoutmobile.com/optOut).

### 6\. What about interest-based advertising?

We follow the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising (about the collection and use of data for interest-based advertising) and expect third parties to comply with the disclosure and notification program specified by principles. This means that third parties collecting and using this data are asked to provide a standard icon/link in or near their advertisements that will provide you with additional data about their privacy and advertising practices, as well as with the opportunity to directly opt-out of having your information collected. To stop receiving interest-based advertising, [click here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).
